halfwaymag.com 2008-09-19

# halfwaymag.com » Privacy Policy

**halfwaymag.com Privacy Policy**  
ver. 27 april, 2005

Halfway encourages freedom of information, while asserting that a right to privacy is of utmost importance. As a result, we have the following guidelines and proceedures regarding your privacy. We know that your privacy is important, and strive to maintain a strong policy against any breech.

**Data Collection:**  
\- Halfwaymag.com collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a page on this site. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.  
\- For crew members or contributors, any information collected for a “crew page” is provided by said member, and alterations, amendments, and/or deletion of such information is the responsibility of the member.  
\- Any information collected, either from referral, contact/inquiry forms, and but not limited to email, is never given or sold to any third parties. We don’t like spam either.

**Cookies:**  
At any point during your visit, a cookie may be sent to your computer. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

For Microsoft users, you can visit [this site](http://www.microsoft.com/resources/documentation/windows/xp/all/proddocs/en-us/sec_cook.mspx) for more information regarding this item.  
For Apple users, you can visit [this site](http://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/aboutcookies.html) for more information regarding this item.  
For other users, please review your respective distributors/manufacturers website or owner’s manual.

**Intellectual Property:**  
The halfwaymag.com logo is copyright © 2005 by halfwaymag.com, and protected under the Creative Commons license. All information, articles, graphics, contained within this site, unless otherwise noted or directed to a third party website, is protected under this license. Any unauthorized use of any, all, or part of these is in direct violation of the Creative Commons license.

**Information Sharing:**  
In an effort to reduce the amount of spam already abound, we do not distribute, give, sell, or otherwise provide any personal information with any third party.  
\- If you are a crew member, the information you provide can be altered, amended, deleted, or otherwise changed provided you contact the correct crew member.

**Security of Information:**  
We take all measures of which we are able to maintain security with your information, and restrict access to your information to crew members with pertinent clearance.

**Links/Outside websites:**  
Halfway holds no responsibility of the content on outside websites, or those linked to on any page or article. This policy is designed for this site alone.

**Advertisements:**  
Google AdSense may be used on this site. What this service does is collect information on the particular page and then provide relavant links in the advertisements based upon the searched text. This is a third party script that does not collect any personal information, though does track the click-through and referrer. More information about this service can be found [here](http://www.google.com/adsense/).

For other advertisers we may release non-identifying information relating to the site statistics only. Unique visitors, hits, and other related information, while no personal information will ever be released.

**Policy Changes:**  
This policy may change without notice. Regardless the scale of change, it is the users responsibility to accustom themselves with and review this policy from time to time. The version of this policy is located at the top of this page. Previous versions can be viewed when there has been more than one.

If you have other questions, comments, or concerns regarding this policy, or are unsure of usage, you can contact privacy[at]halfwaymag.com.
